Ronney Sanchez

Lawrence, Massachusetts, United States

sanchezronney@gmail.com

9789026507

linkedin.com/in/ronney-sanchez-20a263146

Summary

I enrolled at UMASS Lowell to study Computer Science. I have experience with C/C++, Java, HTML, CSS, Python, and JavaScript. In JAVA, I used the Unified Modeling Language, as known as the UML diagram, to create member variables, and methods within a class and instantiate into objects. In C++ I used the Simple and Fast Multimedia Library to create program animations in a window screen.

Experience



Machine Operator

MilliporeSigma

Jun 2022 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Cell Coordinator

Automatic Port Bonder

Manual Port Bonder

Leak (Integrity) Testing

Make Bags

Forming interchangeable parts together to form an end product



Machine Operator

Randstad USA

Sep 2021 - Jun 2022 (10 months)

Make bags

Manual Port Bonder

Automatic Port Bonder

Forming interchangeable parts together for an end product



M Produce Clerk

Demoulas Super Markets, Inc.

Aug 2020 - Sep 2021 (1 year 2 months)



Sacker

Demoulas Super Markets, Inc.

Jun 2014 - Aug 2020 (6 years 3 months)

Education



University of Massachusetts Lowell

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science 2018 - 2019

Northern Essex Community College

Associate of Science - AS, Computer and Information Sciences, General 2015 - 2017

Lawrence High School

High School Diploma 2010 - 2014

Skills

Manufacturing • Microsoft Office • Customer Service • Java • C++ • C • JavaScript • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Machine Operation